Good evening everyone.
>> Um would just like to start off again to
thank the Ram organization, the Kroni
family, specifically Mr. Stan and Josh
for allowing Shawn to give me this
unbelievable opportunity to fill in as
head coach. Can't be thankful enough.
Also, thank you to Mr. Kevin Demoff, Les
Sneed, and Tony Pastor who've known me
since my start here and they've watched
me accelerate throughout my career. I
couldn't be more thankful. I think it's
very important to acknowledge that these
young men went out there and played
against a starting crew from another
team. They fought. They fought
competitively and they did it together.
Usually when you go through ups and
downs of life, it's all about how you
respond. And I couldn't be more happy to
lead a group of men that went out there
and responded together and collectively.
Coach Levy always talks about our style
of play. Playing fast, fundamentally
sound, attacking, being situationally
smart, taking care of the ball and
taking it away. And I think in all
facets of the game today, you see that
to be represented. Couldn't be more
proud to lead this group.
>> Coach, I got to ask you this question.
Are you are Bennett going to take the
offensive line out to dinner because
some young men did a hell of a job of
allowing you guys to go down to get to
win a touchdown.
>> Yes, they did an unbelievable job. You
know, I think in this game I I've
learned, you know, my first opportunity
NFL was with the offensive line and
running backs and I really understand
how important it is for the game to
start up front. Uh even when they broke
the huddle, they they they took they
took the field with a charge. Uh they
aggressively attacked the line of
scrimmage and they protected and they
gave us some opportunities. More
importantly, on those long drives and
maybe didn't come out with the points, I
just made sure I encouraged them because
I saw the fight for us to be able to
punch it in together.
>> You got two shots there at the
two-minute drill there at the end. What
stood out to you about just his demeanor
during those periods?
>> The response. You know, you're going to
hear me say response a couple times in
this press conference. So I think it's
uh very important to you when you give
up a interception the way you do in that
situation and then you come back and you
just respond. That's what life's about
and that's what we want to see
specifically from a quarterback who was
high stakes and you know anytime you
gamble in that situation it could be
difficult but he wasn't and he was
trying to be aggressive and was very
very important that we acknowledge that.
Uh I just really understand his cool
calm demeanor. We've all seen him win a
couple national championships in college
and you see some of that thread work of
his confidence and his belief in his
teammates and the same that they have in
him. Coach, um,
>> how much of a confidence builder was
that last drive for a young quarterback
like St?
>> Oh, it's unbelievable. You know, earlier
we talked about establishing our style
of play. I talked about being
situationally aware. We were in an ozone
situation, a situation that we've, you
know, we've practiced multiple times and
to see us go out there and executed, but
also with some younger receivers that
stepped stepped up. That was awesome.
>> Uh, Matthew Stafford was scheduled to
work out today before the game. Can you
take us through what happened there?
>> Yeah, at any point at this point in
time, anything regarding Mr. Stafford.
I'm going to wait for coach Muvea to
address you guys on Monday.
>> Was he at the game you ran the team
today? Was he on the sideline or here
today?
>> Anything regarding Mr. Stafford? I'm
going to let Sean go ahead and regard
it. I'll be honest with you, I was so
tapped into the ones that had jerseys
on, I wouldn't be able to honestly
answer that second.
>> How do you describe uh St.Son's growth
over the last couple of years and where
he is now? Even his body language of
playing looks like, okay, now I belong.
And I'm not so sure that was the case
before.
>> That's right. Well, we talk about
communication both being verbal and
non-verbal, right? And that means a lot,
especially as a leader, and you can see
through his body language, his
disposition, and his continued steady
state that he's had a lot of physical,
emotional, and I'd say spiritual growth
as well.
>> Coach, can you talk about Jar KZ Hunter
and just how his running style was kind
of violent, but at the same time, he was
very productive. How how do you see him
growing in the next preseason? He has a
unique style of running that's a little
bit different than some of the other
backs. And I think anytime you can have
that versatility only makes you stronger
offensively. Uh there was a joke in the
defensive back room during camp. We said
we guarantee whoever hits him the first
play is probably not going to make that
tackle. He does a good job running
behind his pads and staying forward and
for offensive line. Uh that's all they
want to see is get those chains moving
and it keeps easier for the quarterback
and for the offensive coordinator to
stack plays.
>> What did you think of AJ Green's day?
>> I thought AJ really came out hot. You
know, I think the thing that we
understand really early is they were
taking those three by one isolations
into the boundary and after a couple
plays back to back, he kind of stood up
and realized what it was going to be.
Um, and I think that was with their
first group where they were trying to
get quick and easy throws and kind of
explosive plays to kind of get those
guys out. And I was very, very proud on
how he responded.
>> You had a lot of younger players out
there vying for jobs. Who stood out to
you that we may not have noticed?
>> Yeah. Well, I mean, it's very hard not
to give respect to all the receivers. I
mean, that entire young crew, I mean, no
matter if it was Edwards with the long,
if it was Presley at the end, if it was
uh, you know, True, making sure he got
in that position. I mean, it's
unbelievable how much our young
receivers really uh just took took the
bull by his horns today. And I also want
to give a shout out to some of the
younger players and playing on defense
because sometimes defensively when
there's nothing to really acknowledge,
that means they did their job. And uh,
that's a hard thing sometimes to
understand in this NFL, but I want to
give them respect. And again, shout out
to my leader, co coach Chris Schula,
because he did a phenomenal job calling
the game and uh making sure it fit with
our offense
>> in between that interception and that
game-winning drive. What was your
message to Stson?
>> Reset, breathe. You know, we're all here
for a reason. Um and then what we do is
we respond to them. People are looking
more for our response than necessarily
our actions and those things carry
weight and I wanted them to know that I
was with them and I just wanted them to
keep fighting.
>> What was today? Sorry,
>> last one. Sorry. What was today like for
you as you thought about this moment,
but even like the pregame talk, the
postgame handshake with the coach? You
had some words for Harbaugh. I don't
know if you could share that, but like
just the entire day, how did it live up
to the expectations that you had?
>> Well, as coaches, we're professional
critics, right? And at the same time,
I'm doing that immediately to myself.
What are some things that I could have
done better? Coach Harbaugh and I have
known each other for quite some time. Uh
when I was a young coach in the NFL, he
actually tried to get me to come to
University of Michigan a couple times.
So, we've known each other throughout
our career. Uh, and it's just the kudos,
the respect for each other. Uh, he's
known me since I was a young coach and
he was just giving kudos to my
progression. Um, and I'm sorry, I can't
remember the other part of your
>> entire day. Yes. Like the drive here
knowing that this would be your team on
this particular day.
>> Well, you know, my father always said,
"Luck is when preparation meets
opportunity." This is something I've
been preparing for for quite some time.
Uh, it's something that I'm proud and I
understand that I'm standing on the
shoulders of those who've come before
me. So, I think it's very important that
I represent this thing correctly. Uh,
you know, so far from the game, I
thought everything was pretty good.
Maybe after that long explosive
touchdown, I could have gone for two to
put us in a field goal winning
situation. I'm already thinking about
that because that's something we could
have done to be a little bit better. Uh,
but that's my job and I think if my
players know I'm trying to get better,
they'll only do the same thing.
>> Thanks.
>> Thank you guys. Thank you.
Aubrey was talking about how impressed
he was with the way you reset between
that interception and your two shots at
the two-minute drill. Like what what
were you kind of going through just to
get back on the right track there?
>> You know, they made a it was a great
play. Um
>> yeah, it was hard to see. Um it's really
good play and uh and then you know, we
got to go win a football game and our
defense did a great job of giving us
that second opportunity after we didn't
convert on the on the first one. Um so
yeah, I don't know. Just play the next
play.
this preseason game you take a lot of
reps. First game you've been taking a
lot of reps. Would you say now the game
is kind of slowing down for you as
you're going out there?
>> Uh yeah, I mean I I think I'm confident
in uh you know our calls and uh and
getting the job done obviously uh you
know there's some stuff that we got to
go clean up. Uh but yeah, I'd say so.
>> Was Matthew on the sideline with you
guys today?
>> You know, I was you know so locked in
each and every snap I didn't really
didn't really see. Stson, what are your
thought on all those looking receivers
that caught touch?
>> Yeah, playing I mean
playing really playing really well. Um,
you know, they're fighting uh you know,
there's two fourth down conversions on
two different drives maybe on the same.
I'm really tired right now. Uh but uh uh
yeah, just fighting for me. Playing
playing great. Playing great.
>> After that throw to Mario, looked like
Mike had a big smile on his face when
you got to the sideline. What did he
tell you after that play?
you after the drive or
>> a 38 yard to Mario
>> on the fourth down
>> touchdown.
>> Oh, on the touchdown. Yeah, that was
that was sweet. Um there was just like a
look in uh in in practice that was kind
of like that and you know stepped up
great protection. He ran a great route
kind of stuck it in there. Safety kind
of hung over there on the left hash and
just getting the ball up and down. Um
that was a fun one. That was a fun play.
>> What did Mike say to you when you came
back to the sideline after that? Um, I
honestly don't know, but he we just, you
know, he was kind of smiling and uh
yeah, I can't remember exactly what he
said, but yeah.
>> So, let know that you beat a team that
they were playing their ones today. They
were playing all their starters. What
does that mean? I I think uh I think
everybody in our locker room just saw it
as a great opportunity and uh you know
we were excited to go out there because
they're going to be a really good
football team and uh yeah, we just saw a
great opportunity and uh you know just
you know uh like the coaches say just
testing our rules right now. We're not
really game planning and they're not
either. Um but uh yeah, just going out
there and compete.
>> What does that last drive do for you as
far as your confidence?
>> Oh man. Um
I don't know. just uh that uh you know
it's not over till it is. Um just just
keep going and um keep swinging. Um
yeah. Uh and yeah,
>> what's the difference from year one to
year three in terms of just your comfort
and being out there and your command of
the team?
>> Yeah, I think we're back to playing
football more so than um whatever it
might be. You know what I'm saying? I
think that's a lot of when you first get
here, at least for me. Uh, and when I
say here, I mean the NFL or a new
league. It was the same going from high
school to college and the college to the
NFL. It's just like I don't know
whatever might be, but uh, you know,
it's football and um, and so I think
that's the best explanation. Not that
that was a good one, but
>> how about the fight for the job? Every
year is a little bit different.
Circumstances are different. How do you
feel now from a confidence standpoint?
It's like, hey, I'm getting it done out
there and you're battling for a job.
>> Yeah. I mean, I think um again, it's
just every single play, every single
snap going out there. I think uh um all
you know, coaches say like, you know, it
it comes from within and I think we
we've got a great group of guys in
there. You know, every single person
that you know, the motivation comes from
an within. It's not necessarily
external. Um but uh yeah, just uh
attacking each and every play.
>> How would you describe the feeling on
the field when you're playing with the
kind of confidence and swagger that
you're playing with tonight? Was that
feel like
>> um I don't know. I just I feel like um
I'm just listening to the play call and
trying to execute it, you know, to my
best ability.
>> You were trying to calm the your
teammates down before that two-point.
You were going through like a breathing
exercise. Was that even hard for you to
kind of calm down?
>> Yeah, I think it was for me as much as
it was for them, you know. Um just, you
know, we let's go execute and you know,
they made a good stop on that one, but
um you know, yeah, just we got this next
play. um let's go execute that one.
>> If if Shawn were to turn to you for
whatever reason early in the season, you
feel like you'd be prepared to step in
and run with the one?
>> Yeah, I think um again, it's the same
thing. You know, we're just trying to
execute every single play and uh um and
do it the best for for the Rams.
>> Couple more. What does this victory mean
to you?
>> Uh
it it it was pretty cool. I'm not going
to lie, cuz it was uh I was tired out
there. It was uh that was a hard fault
one and I think everybody out there uh
at the end and you know defense getting
us the ball back um it was uh it it was
it was pretty sweet.
>> Was it tired just from like the number
of throws you were going through or like
>> Yeah, I think just um Yeah, I think just
the number of plays, throws, whatever it
was.
>> Last one.
>> Um congrats on the win and was there
anything special you saw in your early
passes to Xavier because he had a couple
of very good catches. Was there anything
you saw or there was a read there that
you noticed?
>> Um,
I mean, Xavier Smith is an awesome
football player. If I'm going to be
totally honest with you, that feels like
it was four years ago, the first
quarter. And, uh, I'm going to have to
go rewatch the film, but he's an awesome
football player, so sorry about that.
>> Hey guys,